Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 2: Boxes 23-44 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- Public Service Research Council - House Organs, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Item 119: Forewarned! Vol. 16 No. 9, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. October 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 120: Forewarned! Vol. 16 No. 10, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. November 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 121: Forewarned Vol. 16 No. 11, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. December 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 122: Forewarned! Vol. 16 No. 8, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. September 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 123: Forewarned! Vol. 17 No. 1, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. January 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 124: Forewarned! Vol. 17 No. 3, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. March 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 125: Forewarned! Vol. 17 No. 2, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. February 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 126: Forewarned! Vol. 17 No. 6, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. June 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 127: Forewarned! Vol. 17 No. 7, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. July 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 128: Forewarned Vol.. 17 No. 9, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. September 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 129: Forewarned! Vol. 17 No. 10, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. October 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 130: Forewarned! Vol. 18 No. 1, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. January 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 131: Forewarned! Vol. 17 no. 11, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. November 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 132: Forewarned! Vol. 18 No. 2, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. February 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 133: Forewarned! Vol. 18 No. 3, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. March 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 134: Forewarned! Vol. 18 No. 6, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. August 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 135: Forewarned! Vol. 18 No. 4, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. April 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 136: Letter to Labot Management Documentaion, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Item 137: Forewarned! Vol. 19 No. 2, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Item 138: Letter to Labor Management Documentation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Item 139: Forewarned! Vol. 19 No. 5, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. May/ June 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 140: Forewarned! Vol. 19 No. 4, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    By Public Service Research Council. April 1994. Item is in English.
  - Item 141: Letter to Labor Management Documentation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Pullman Incorporated - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Benefits: Highlights for Active Employees, Publication (Box 26, Folder 16)
    By Pullman Incorporated. January 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Performance Evaluation: Instruction, Publication (Box 26, Folder 16)
    By Pullman Incorporated. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Pullman Standard: Employment Application, Publication (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Quaker Oats Company - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: New Performance Planning and Review Form, Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
    By Quaker Oats Company. May 19, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Six Month Performance Review and Approval, Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
    By Quaker Oats Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Performance Planning and Review, Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Performance Planning and Review (continuation sheet), Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Performance Review Workshet/ Performance Analysis, Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Performance Planning and Review for Corporate Staff Departments, Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Performance Planning and Review, Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: You and Flextime, Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: Overtime Pay-Summer Hours, Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
    By Quaker Oats Company. April 19, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: All Quaker Employees Located at the Mart, Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
    By Quaker Oats Company. April 18, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Quaker Quarterly, Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Item 12: Quaker!, Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Quaker Oats - "Quaker and You", Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: 1983 Quaker Benefits in Brief, Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Health Maintenance Organizations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Your Rights as a Plan Participant, Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Stock Sharing: Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Retirement Income, Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Life Insurance: Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Dental Care: Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: The Health Incentive Plan, Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Item 10: Disability Income, Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Item 11: The Salary Administration Program, Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
- R.J. Reynolds Industries Incorporated - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Golden Leaves, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
    By R.J. Reynolds Industries Incorporated. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Career in Sales with R.J. Reynolds Tobacco USA: Innovative, Professional, Successful, Respected, Determined, Committed to Excellence, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: Our 100th Anniversary, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 9: Health Care: Winston-Salem Health Care Plan, Inc.: Member's Benefits, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 10: Dental Care: Member's Benefits, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 11: Employee Benefit Plans: Regular, Full-Time Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 12: Performance Evaluation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 13: Non-Exempt Salaried Personnel, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 14: R.J. Reynolds Industries Inc., Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 15: Building Strength on Strength, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
    By R.J. Reynolds Industries Incorporated. February 16, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: A Tour of Whitaker Park, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 17: Tobaccoville Manufacturing Center, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 18: Davie County Leaf Processing & Storage, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 19: Agricultural Programs, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
- R.R. Donnelley, Publication (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Donnelley: Dynamic Leadership in a Dynamic Industry, Publication (Box 26, Folder 20)
    By R.R. Donnelley. Item is in English.
- Railway Labor Executives Association, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The History of the Railway Labor Executives Association, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
    By Railway Labor Executives Association. May 18, 1926. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: What Every Railroad Worker Should Know About Alcohol and Drug Testing, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
    By Railway Labor Executives Association. March 1, 1987. Item is in English.
- Ralston Purina, Publication (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Check Us Ot at Checkerbaord Square, Publication (Box 26, Folder 22)
    By Ralston Purina. Item is in English.
- Raytheon Company, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: For Your Share: The Raytheon Stock Ownership Plan, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
    By Raytheon Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Raytheon Magazine Fall 1985, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: Raytheon: There's Only One Way, Standards of Business Behavior & Ethics, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
- RCA - handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Health and Life Insurance Plan: Salary Employees RCA Corporation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    By RCA. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Long Term Disability Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: Employee Suggestion System: Using Ideas to Change Things, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: A Career Spectrum that Spans, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 6: A Reference to Employment Practices Compensation Benefits, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 7: A Career Spectrum that Spans, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 8: Standards of Business Conduct, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Resettlement Administration, Publication (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Greendale, Wisconsin: Resettlement Administration, Publication (Box 26, Folder 25)
    By Resettlement Administration. Item is in English.
- Religion and Labor Conference, Publication (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Coalitions for Today's Challenges, Publication (Box 26, Folder 26)
    By Religion and Labor Conference. June 24-27, 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: AFL-CIO Endorses Religion and Labor Effort, Publication (Box 26, Folder 26)
    By Religion and Labor Conference. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: National Conference on Religion & Labor, Publication (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Republic Steel, Publication (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Republic Reports No. 1, Publication (Box 26, Folder 27)
    By Republic Steel. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Repuiblic Reports No. 1, Publication (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Republic Steel: And That Can Make the Difference: Some Thoughts on Where you go from Here, Publication (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: Republic Steel: Plans and Facilities, Publication (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Item 5: Republic Reports No. 1, Publication (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Item 6: Republic Steel, Publication (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Item 7: Republic Reports No. 2, Publication (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Retraining and Re-employment Administration, Publication (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: To Organize To Operate: Your Community Advisory Center for Veterans and Others, Publication (Box 26, Folder 28)
    By Retraining and Reemployment Administration. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Interview in Counseling: A Professionally Prepared Outline of Interviewing Procedure, for use of Community Advisory Centers, Publication (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Rexnord, Publication (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Before You Say "I'll Take the Job" some Thoughts about Careers at Rexnord, Publication (Box 26, Folder 29)
    By Rexnord. Item is in English.
- Reynolds Aluminum, Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Some Questions and Answers About, Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
    By Reynolds Aluminum. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Supervisor's Guide: Reynolds Employee Assistance Program, Publication (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Rheem Manufacturing Company, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Benefit Program for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
    By Rheem Manufacturing Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Welcome to Rheem Air Conditioning Division, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: elcome to Rheem Water Heater Division, Publication (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Rhode Island Working Women, Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Woman's Work Vol. 6 No. 1, Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
    By Rhode Island Working Women. January- February 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Woman's Work Vol. 5 No. 5, Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
    By Rhode Island Working Women. September, October 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Woman's Work Vol. 5 No. 2, Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
    By Rhode Island Working Women. March, April 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Woman's Work Vol. 5 No. 6, Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
    By Rhode Island Working Women. November, December 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Working Papers Vol. 9 No. 1, Publication (Box 26, Folder 32)
    By Rhode Island Working Women. September 1987. Item is in English.
- Richardson-Merrell Inc., Publication (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Imagination, Individuality, Reach: That's What Makes the Difference at Richardson-Merrell Inc., Publication (Box 26, Folder 33)
    By Richardson-Merrell Inc. Item is in English.
- Rich Products, Publication (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Agrees to Sell Certain Facilities in Lake City, Publication (Box 26, Folder 34)
    By Rich Products. April 24, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Rich's The People, Products and Potential, Publication (Box 26, Folder 34)
    By Rich Products. Item is in English.
- Richardson-Vicks, Publication (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Introducing Richardson-Vicks, Publication (Box 26, Folder 35)
    By Richardson Vicks. Item is in English.
- Rockefeller Foundation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Into the Working World, Publication (Box 26, Folder 36)
    By Rockefeller Foundation. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Into the Working World, Publication (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Rockwell International - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Rockwell International: Where Science Gets Down to Business, Publication (Box 26, Folder 37)
    By Rockwell International. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Rockwell News Vol. 9 No. 10, Publication (Box 26, Folder 37)
    By Rockwell International. October 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Rockwell International, Publication (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Item 4: History: Rockwell International, Publication (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Item 5: 1987 Directory for Products/ Sales/ Services, Publication (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Item 6: Rockwell News Vol. 14 No. 8, Publication (Box 26, Folder 37)
    By Rockwell International. December 1986. Item is in English.
- Rocky Mountain-Occupation Safety & Health, Publication (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: You Can Make Your Workplace Safer, We can help, Publication (Box 26, Folder 38)
    By Rocky Mountain-Occupation Safety and Health. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Your Back and Your Job: A Worker's Survival Guide, Publication (Box 26, Folder 38)
- Roy A. Walters Associates, Publication (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: A Checklist of Key Factors in Company-Wide Transformation Efforts, Publication (Box 26, Folder 39)
    By Roy A. Walters Associates. Item is in English.
- Rubber Manufacturers Association, Publication (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Who Needs Rubber?, Publication (Box 26, Folder 40)
    By Rubber Manufactureers Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: How Your Gifted Hands Can Put You on Your Own Two Feet Fast!, Publication (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Item 3: Steel Settlement, Publication (Box 26, Folder 40)
    By Rubber Manufacturers Association. April 17, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Cost of Living Clauses in the Rubber Manufacturing Industry, Publication (Box 26, Folder 40)
    By Rubber Manufacturers Association. June 10, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Excerpt from Constitution and By-Laws, Publication (Box 26, Folder 40)
    By Rubber Manufacturers Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Career and Educational Opportunities in the Rubber and Plastics Industry, Publication (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Item 7: Rubber Highlights Vol. 25 No. 2, Publication (Box 26, Folder 40)
    By Rubber Manufacturers Association. February 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Catalog of Free Educational Aids (Publications & Films) From the Tire and Rubber Industry, Publication (Box 26, Folder 40)
- Rutgers University, New Brunswick, N.J.: Institute of Management & Labor Relations -- Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Another group of decision made by arbitrators under C. 85 of the New Jersey Employer-Employee Relations Institute of Management and Labor Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 41)
    By Institute of Management and Labor Relations Rutgers, the State University of New Jersey. June 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: An additional group of cases heard by New Jersey arbitrators under chapter 85, Public Laws of 1977, have een analyzed by Mr. Petro Stawnychy and appear below, Publication (Box 26, Folder 41)
    By Institute of Management and Labor Relations Rutgers, the State University of New Jersey. May 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Agency Shop Bill Becomes Law No. 37, Publication (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Item 4: Representation for Bargaining in New Jersey State Government No. 38, Publication (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Item 5: New Jersey Public Employer-Employee Relations No. 1, Publication (Box 26, Folder 41)
    By Institute of Management and Labor Relations Rutgers, the State University of New Jersey. July 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: New Jersey Public Employer-Employee Relations No. 38, Publication (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Item 7: New Jersey Public Employer-Employee Relations No. 23, Publication (Box 26, Folder 41)
    By Institute of Management and Labor Relations Rutgers, the State University of New Jersey. April 22, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: A Report from IMLR: Representation for Bargaining in New Jersey Public Universities, Publication (Box 26, Folder 41)
    By Institute of Management and Labor Relations Rutgers, the State University of New Jersey. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: New Jersey Public Employer-Employee Relations No. 24, Publication (Box 26, Folder 41)
    By Institute of Management and Labor Relations Rutgers, the State University of New Jersey. May 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: An Information Note from the Institute of Management and Labor Relations No. 22, Publication (Box 26, Folder 41)
    By Institute of Management and Labor Relations Rutgers, the State University of New Jersey. March 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: New Jersey Public Employer-Employee Relations No. 25, Publication (Box 26, Folder 41)
    By Institute of Management and Labor Relations Rutgers, the State University of New Jersey. July 8, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: An Information Note from the Institute of Management and Labor Relations Library No. 26, Publication (Box 26, Folder 41)
    By Institute of Management and Labor Relations Rutgers, the State University of New Jersey. August 8, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: An Information Note from the Institute of Management and Labor Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 41)
    By Institute of Management and Labor Relations Rutgers, the State University of New Jersey. October 13, 1983. Item is in English.
- Ryder System, Inc., Publication (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Selections, Publication (Box 26, Folder 42)
    By Ryder System, Inc. Item is in English.
- Shipbuilders Council of America, Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Pride in Being Part of the Team, Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
    By Manufacturers Hanover Trust Company. February 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: 1987 In Review: Manpower and Labor Issues Report, Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
    By Shipbuilders Council of America. Item is in English.
- Sibson & Company, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: 1988 Compensation Planning Survey, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
    By Sibson & Company. Item is in English.
- Signal Companies, Inc., Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Signal Difference: A Case for a Career with Us, Twelve Young Men and Women Talk About their Work and Opportunities, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
    By Signal Companies, Inc. Item is in English.
- Smithkline Corporation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Momentum: Smithkline Corporation Management Access Program, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By Smithkline Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Smithkline and You Folder, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Momentum: Smithkline Corporation Folder, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: SmithKline, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: News Release: SmithKline Beecham Index Shows Drug Use Decline Among Workers Tested in 1991, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By Smithkline Corporation. August 5, 1991. Item is in English.
- SCM Corp., Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Ithaca Journal: Letters to the Journal, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
    By SCM Corporation. March 23. Item is in English.
- St. Regis Paper Company - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Our WorldYou can Help Shape it., Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    By St. Regis Paper Company. Item is in English.
- San Diego Gas & Electric Company, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Voice of Energy, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    By San Diego Gas & Electric Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Performance Appraisal Summary, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Employee Evaluation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Performance Evaluation (Clerical & Technical Employees), Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Update: Published Weekly for SDG&E Employees Vol. 1 No. 47, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    By San Diego Gas & Electric Company. December 1, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The 10% Solution: Your Challenge to Begin the Search, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Audience of One, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
- San Diego Gas & Electric Company "Information for Employees", 1986; Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Information for Employees: General Information, Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Santa Fe Industries - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Give me a Place to Stand, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
    By Santa Fe Industries. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Railway News Volume 1 Number 6, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
    By Santa Fe Industries. March 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Pace Volume 4 No. 1, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
    By Santa Fe Industries. February 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Energy-Efficient Transportation Energy-Producing Resources, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Opportunity, Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Saturn Corporation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Saturn Corporation Pertinent Dates, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
    By Saturn Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Saturn Site Dedication, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
    By Richard G. LeFauve. April 8, 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: For Release, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
    By Saturn Corporation. July 29, 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: News from the UAW: UAW Region & Director George H. Smith, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
    By Saturn Corporation. May 24, 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Site Facts: Saturn Corporation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
    By Saturn Corporation. Spring 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: News from the UAW: UAW Vice-President Donald F. Ephlin, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)